American Scholar Records
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Part III: Production File, 1984-2006 (Box III:98-199)
  - 2004 (vol. 73)
    - Winter
      - Articles, (6 folders); (5 folders) (Box III:181)
      - Books, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box III:182)
      - Departments, (4 folders)
      - Miscellany, (2 folders)
      - Reader replies
    - Spring
      - Articles, (2 folders); (8 folders); (1 folder) (Box III:183, Box III:184)
      - Books, (3 folders)
      - Departments, (5 folders)
      - Miscellany, (2 folders) (Box III:185)
      - Reader replies
    - Summer
      - Articles, (5 folders) (Box III:186)
      - Books, (2 folders)
      - Departments, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box III:187)
      - Miscellany
      - Poetry
      - Reader replies
    - Autumn
      - Articles, (8 folders); (14 folders); (5 folders) (Box III:188, Box III:189)
      - Books, (2 folders)
      - Departments, (4 folders); (2 folders) (Box III:190)
      - Miscellany, (3 folders)
      - Poetry
      - Reader replies
  - 2005 (vol. 74)
    - Winter
      - Articles, (3 folders); (5 folders) (Box III:191)
      - Arts, (4 folders)
      - Books, (2 folders) (Box III:192)
      - Departments, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany
      - Poetry
    - Spring
      - Articles, (3 folders); (6 folders) (Box III:193)
      - Arts, (3 folders)
      - Books, (2 folders) (Box III:194)
      - Departments, (6 folders)
      - Miscellany, (2 folders)
      - Poetry
    - Summer (Box III:195)
      - Articles, (9 folders)
      - Arts, (3 folders) (Box III:196)
      - Books, (3 folders)
      - Departments, (4 folders)
      - Miscellany (Box III:197)
      - Poetry
    - Autumn
      - Articles, (6 folders); (2 folders) (Box III:198)
      - Arts, (3 folders)
      - Books, (2 folders)
      - Departments, (3 folders); (4 folders) (Box III:199)
      - Miscellany, (2 folders)
      - Poetry
  - 2006 (vol. 75)
    - Winter
      - Article